juicerecipes.com 2017-02-24

# Privacy Policy | Juice Recipes

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use your personal information in connection with our advertising, content, e-commerce, promotional and service programs and other business activities (the "Program") and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services and the sites of our advertisers.

## What Information We Collect

When you visit our site we may collect two types of information: (a) personal information you actively choose to disclose and (b) information about you that is collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties in a way not visible to you.

  1. _Information you actively choose to provide._ By choosing to become a newsletter subscriber, at no cost, by disclosing information such as your email address and name. During the process of registering on our site, participating in various offers, completing surveys, or sending us emails or correspondence, we collect additional information that you may disclose, including for example email, name, facebook information, pinterest information, health information and personal preferences regarding lifestyle, products or services.
  2. _Passive information collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties._ We collect some information about you simply by virtue of you connecting to our web site. Our servers automatically identify your computer by its internet protocol ("IP") address, a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. In addition, to participate in our program you must allow cookies to be active on your system. Cookies are a feature of web browser software (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) that allows web servers to recognize which computer is used to access a web site. Cookies simplify subsequent interactions on our site and streamline your transactions on related web pages. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visits, the site pages you viewed, the time spent at each page, and the web sites you visited just before and just after our site. You can disable the cookie function by following the instructions in the "help" section of your browser. However, doing so will likely make it impossible for our system to properly recognize you when you visit our sites, and consequently may make your participation in our program more difficult or impossible. In addition to the information you provide or that is collected automatically from our system, we may obtain information about you from our marketing partners or other third parties, and we combine that information with the information you actively provide or that is automatically collected by our servers. We also use “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) (as [amended for government websites](http://www.howto.gov/sites/default/files/google-analytics-tos-amendment.pdf)) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser. 

The term "Information" is used in this policy to refer to both types of information described above, as well as any Information that you provide to us directly by email, phone (including any phone number displayed via caller ID), text or SMS message, U.S. mail or through any other written or oral communication with us.

## How We Use And Share The Information Collected

We use your Information to administer our business activities, provide customer services such as technical support, distribute information about changes to our site, and send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you and to contact you or use your Information for any other purpose. We send communications to you ourselves so that we may contact you for any purpose by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication.

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/)

## OPT-IN NOTICE: By Participating, You Expressly "Opt In" To Receive Information And Grant Us Permission To Send You Information

By submitting your email to us through user account creation or our 30 Day Challenge, you expressly opt in to receive future information about products and services from us or we will send you information regarding products and services from a third party that we think you may be interested in.

In addition, in the event we consider a transaction involving the purchase or sale of our assets or stock, other companies may review our records, including your Information, to make business decisions about the transaction. Likewise, your Information may be transferred to third parties in the event of the sale or acquisition of our company or any of its assets. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant banks, our internet service provider, etc.) also may have access to your information in performing their services.

## Special Note About Information You Provide Directly To Our Advertisers.

You are able to access certain advertiser's sites through our site. When you opt to receive information or sign up for an offer from an advertiser, you may be doing so through third party sites and with other companies over which we have no control. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you wish to opt out of those advertisers' mailings, you must do so directly with such advertisers or as otherwise provided on or through their sites.

## Third Party Ad Servers

We may serve advertisements within our Web Site either ourselves or by allowing other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to do so. In addition, some of our advertisers may use the services of third-party ad networks. Some of these third-party ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third-party ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, third-party ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows a third-party ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or third-party ad networks. Those third-party ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the web site of either the individual third-party ad network.

## Security Of Your Information

We use reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Information. However, nearly all Internet transmissions pass through many servers not controlled by us, and therefore we cannot guarantee that any information you provide us or we collect will not be intercepted or altered in that process.

## How You Can Choose To "Opt Out" Of Receiving Further Information About Products Or Services

If at any time you do not wish to receive further information about products or services from us and wish us to cease providing your Information to third parties, you may chose to "opt-out" through the Unsubscribe/"Opt-Out" page of our site or by written request sent by mail to our Customer Service Manager at the following address: Juice Recipes, PO BOX 1747 Tampa, FL 33601

Juice Recipes  
PO BOX 1747  
Tampa, FL 33601  

We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to 30 (30) business days from our receipt of your request for the change to be fully effective. If you later give us a clear statement that you want to receive emails from us or our advertisers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request.

## How To Correct, Delete Or Access Your Information

If you wish to access, delete or correct the information you have provided to us through this site, please contact us through the Contact Us section of our site or through written request sent by mail to the Customer Service Manager at the address listed above.

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Last Updated: April 20th, 2015
